{"test_questions": [[{"question": "When 1100010 is divided by 0101, what will be the decimal remainder?", "opta": "2", "optb": "3", "optc": "4", "optd": "6", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What are the two types of basic adder circuits?", "opta": "half adder and full adder", "optb": "half adder and parallel adder", "optc": "asynchronous and synchronous", "optd": "one's complement and two's complement", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Adding the two's complement of \u201311 + (\u20132) will yield which two's complement answer?", "opta": "1110 1101", "optb": "1111 1001", "optc": "1111 0011", "optd": "1110 1001", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The two's complement system is to be used to add the signed numbers 11110010 and 11110011. Determine, in decimal, the sign and value of each number and their sum.", "opta": "\u201314 and \u201313; \u201327", "optb": "\u2013113 and \u2013114; 227", "optc": "\u201327 and \u201313; 40", "optd": "\u201311 and \u201316; \u201327", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The fast carry or look-ahead carry circuits found in most 4-bit parallel-adder circuits:", "opta": "increase ripple delay", "optb": "add a 1 to complemented inputs", "optc": "reduce propagation delay", "optd": "determine sign and magnitude", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many basic binary subtraction operations are possible?", "opta": "4", "optb": "3", "optc": "2", "optd": "1", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many basic binary subtraction combinations are possible?", "opta": "4", "optb": "3", "optc": "2", "optd": "1", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Use the two's complement system to add the signed numbers 11110010 and 11110011. Determine, in decimal, the sign and value of each number and  \ntheir sum.", "opta": "\u201314 and \u201313; \u201327", "optb": "\u2013113 and \u2013114; 227", "optc": "\u201327 and \u201313; 40", "optd": "\u201311 and \u201316; \u201327", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The selector inputs to an arithmetic-logic unit (ALU) determine the:", "opta": "selection of the IC", "optb": "arithmetic or logic function", "optc": "data word selection", "optd": "clock frequency to be used", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Adding in binary, the decimal values 26 + 27 will produce a sum of:", "opta": "111010", "optb": "110110", "optc": "110101", "optd": "101011", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Binary subtraction of a decimal 15 from 43 will utilize which two's complement?", "opta": "101011", "optb": "110000", "optc": "011100", "optd": "110001", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When multiplying in binary the decimal values 13 \u00d7 11, what is the third partial product?", "opta": "100000", "optb": "100001", "optc": "0000", "optd": "1011", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The range of an 8-bit two's complement word is from:", "opta": "+12810 to \u201312810", "optb": "\u201312810 to +12710", "optc": "+12810 to \u201312710", "optd": "+12710 to \u201312710", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}